[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 38]
Luo Ge,
look at the world.
People intrigue against
each other.
They are jealous of the talents
and dissipate rumors.
Luo Ge,
you're wrong.
It's not me that made the world like this,
but people raised me
with their desires.
The peace and joy you want
can only last a moment.
You can't control
chaos and darkness.
Get lost!
Go away!
You are still struggling, Luo Ge.
Your perseverance
is as great as that of God of the Moonlight.
But even God of the Moonlight
was defeated by me.
What can you do?
You're just an evil spirit harming the mortal world
in Three Realms.
How dare you call yourself that?
After I replace you,
I'll be the master of Three Realms, and
I will have supreme power.
I will also have
the girl that God of the Moonlight yearns for even when he died.
Why can't I call myself like that?
You are not allowed to touch Liu Shao.
Not allowed?
Unfortunately, it's not up to you.
I'm afraid that at that time, Liu Shao will
come into my arms without hesitation.
How dare you!
Luo Ge,
it seems that you don't understand that
a truly strong person shouldn't have a weakness.
What's going on with the sky?
Can Immortal Palace rain, thunder, and have lightning like the mortal world?
Be careful.
The thunder and lightning
remind me of the scene where the evil spirit
came out ten thousand years ago.
Ten thousand years ago?
That's right.
I just transformed at that time.
It looked like this too.
Later, I found out that
it was because the evil spirit came out.
It was said that there was no sun in the mortal world
for seven days,
and everything stopped growing.
If it weren't for the two immortals,
Three Realms
might have fallen into eternal night,
and all beings
would have been extinguished.
Don't think too much.
The evil spirit has been suppressed for ten thousand years.
His power is no longer as strong as before.
Immortal Luo Ge can handle it.
Luo Ge.
Luo Ge!
Has Luo Ge been...
No.
I can't be controlled by that evil creature.
I have to hang in there.
I have to.
Chaos has appeared.
Luo Ge may have lost his mind.
I...
will hang in there.
Luo Ge,
hang in there.
Why are you
a little different?
Immortal Palace is too boring.
It's time to change it.
I think this appearance
suits Luo Ge.
Besides,
should we
get married?
Get married?
I did ask Master Shang
to prepare for it before,
but many things have happened recently.
Besides, Master Zhuo was petrified,
and Master Shang is not in the mood to handle it,
so
this matter was put off.
I've been waiting for so long.
Why is it still delayed?
So,
how long are you going to hide from me?
I'm still young.
It's not strange for me
not to get married.
It is too late.
We can't
put this matter off anymore.
How about holding the wedding
tomorrow?
Does it have to be in such a hurry?
It is not in a hurry.
I'll manage everything.
I will tell Three Realms that
the person I will marry
is Luo Ge's favorite, Liu Shao.
Do you remember this flower?
Do you remember
who made this flower?
For one person,
I froze the flower here
and let it never wither.
Now I want to use this flower
to reflect that person's heart.
You're right.
Liu Shao is my weakness,
but she is also my armor.
You, some black energy, will never understand the courage
a person can gain
when loving someone.
Ridiculous.
That man said
after experiencing thousands of tribulations
through thousands of years,
he only loves me.
Even if I have experienced thousands of tribulations
through thousands of years,
you are still the only one
I love.
Liu Shao...
You are Luo Ge.
Liu Shao,
it will appear anytime.
I'm running out of time.
You'll be fine.
I'll find some other ways.
♫The begonia is red, but every promise makes it more withered♫
Everything will be fine.
Okay.
I'll try my best to protect my consciousness.
♫It blooms alone, but the wind and rain are more violent♫
I'm waiting for you.
You can make it.
♫Plants are not human beings, and ruthless fruits are planted♫
What did you say?
Luo Ge will be controlled by the evil creature at any time!
The half of his heart
♫How can you forget the innocence and ignorance when we first met?♫
still leaves a disaster.
Even Luo Ge can't suppress it?
Luo Ge wants me to go to Marquis Wu Yang's mansion immediately
♫The butterfly emerges from the chrysalis, but it is difficult to fly to the sky♫
to build more Protection Spells.
He asked you to do it.
Isn't he the one who did all this?
♫The butterfly's wings were broken, and the dream fell without a trace♫
I have injected my divine spirit into Moon Bell.
Even if I am completely occupied by the evil spirit,
♫Because of their greed for the warmth of the fire, they lost each other♫
you can also activate the divine spirit in Wang Bell
to wake me up
so that we can seek a chance to kill the evil spirit.
♫There is a period of youth, and he is waiting for the spring breeze in the coming year♫
Luo Ge!
Are you okay?
Besides,
go to Marquis Wuyang's mansion immediately.
♫How many times do we have to reincarnate♫
Set a new boundary with your immortal energy
♫Before we meet again in the next life?♫
to take a precaution in the mortal world.
And then?
♫Suffer all grief and long hate♫
Then, you have to take the time
to prepare to deal with the evil these days.
♫Reversed right and wrong dreams♫
This time, Three Realms
♫I exiled my thousand-year-old body♫
count on you.
♫Waiting for the ashes to slowly burn in the heart♫
Luo Ge can't leave.
♫Wait until the end of life to see the begonia turn red again♫
Xuan Ling Wood Boundary.
You're right.
Xuan Ling Wood can help him suppress the evil thing.
But you will be tired then.
Yes.
Luo Ge has been standing in front of me
all the time
to protect me from the wind and rain.
This time,
I'll stand in front of Luo Ge
♫How many times do we have to reincarnate♫
and clear the obstacles
♫Before we meet again in the next life?♫
for him.
♫Suffer all grief and long hate♫
♫Reversed right and wrong dreams♫
♫I exiled my thousand-year-old body♫
♫Waiting for the ashes to slowly burn in the heart♫
♫Wait until the end of life to see the begonia turn red again♫
Demon King, please wait a moment.
Immortal,
Demon King in White wants to see you.
Let him in.
Demon King, please.
Have a seat.
What is the matter?
I've been planning to come and apologize,
and stop in to check whether you
are doing well.
I'm fine.
Thank you for your concern.
Luo Ge.
The teacup is empty.
Is there anything wrong
with the half heart?
He Na,
the Luo Ge you will meet next time
might not be the real Luo Ge.
Is the evil spirit really...
Yes.
I didn't expect that
the so-called Immortal
would be the biggest trouble in Three Realms.
I hope
when I lose my mind,
Liu Shao will be as brave as God of the Sun who
has the courage
and the ability to stop me.
Although she's trying to find a way,
I'm afraid that the time is limited and
she won't make it in time.
She has the talent,
but she needs time.
There is a breakthrough on her.
Maybe it can solve this completely.
What breakthrough?
Clear Vine.
Clear Vine
hides in the Qiansha Illusion in Bone Melting Pool.
Clear Vine likes to eat evil spirits.
If it can be used as medicine,
it can stimulate the spirit
and improve people's cultivation.
But Qiansha Illusion makes people confused.
One can't enter unless he is a deity.
Then you can go and get it now.
There's still evil energy in my body.
The Vine may treat me as an evil creature.
Water energy can stop evil spirits.
If I am not enough,
there is also Fu.
Go and see Fu.
Come and protect me later.
Brother,
I know you're disappointed in me.
I made a huge mistake.
But Luo Ning is innocent.
I hope you
can bring her immortal energy
out of Bone Melting Pool.
I'm willing to serve
in Bone Melting Pool until I die.
You are not qualified to die.
You ruined Luo Ning,
Melody race,
and Three Realms.
How can you die?
I can't hold on any longer.
After I die,
you'll be the King of Melody race.
You can't die here.
You must live with Luo Ning's yearning
to atone for your heinous crimes.
Luo Ning cares about Luo Ge the most.
Give him your water energy
with me
and help him find the instrument.
This protection will be counted
as the first thing you do to atone for your crime.
Fu and I will protect you.
Besides,
take this Water Energy Lantern.
It will connect with your inner energy.
If a spirit appears,
it will flash.
By then,
Fu and I will try our best to get you back.
You have to be careful all the time too.
I've entered Qiansha Illusion.
Pay close attention to Water Energy Lantern.
Brother,
look.
It's testing me.
Brother,
Water Energy Lantern is weakening.
Oh no.
It found out.
Luo Ge,
come back!
Luo Ge!
Add water energy.
Luo Ge.
Luo Ge!
It was an emergency.
How did you get out of danger?
It was Luo Ning.
Luo Ning's immortal energy also entered the Boundary.
She saved me.
There was a beam of light.
It lighted up the entire Protection Spell.
The Vine disappeared too.
Let go of my brother.
Later, the Vine recognized me as Immortal,
and that's why it gave the Vine to me.
Fu.
Go back.
The future of Immortal Palace is unpredictable.
Let Fu stay away from trouble
so that he can save his life.
It is also Luo Ning's wish.
Thank you.
I will teach him well.
I won't let him make mistakes again.
Take good care of my sister's immortal energy.
Let's go.
Immortal Master, you're awake.
I dreamed of Fairy Luo Ning just now.
How long did I sleep?
Did she come to see me?
You don't remember.
Fairy has passed away.
What have I done?
I will give you enough power
to let you overturn Three Realms.
What did I do?
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
As long as the person who cast Protection Spell is alive,
the boundary will be solid.
The boundary my brother built is very solid.
Why do you have to build another one?
Is there something wrong
with my brother's body?
It's been ten thousand years.
We've finally come this far.
Can Ge and the Liu Shao
change the fate between
God of the Sun and God of the Moonlight?
It seems that
I need to tell Liu Shao something.
Don't do anything evil.
Do good deeds.
Luo Ning,
are these what you want to tell me?
Now I finally understand.
General Fu is looking for me.
Mr. Tai, let me ask you.
Can my brother recover
if I take away his water energy?
General,
His Majesty only has
Water Spirit Vein and 1000 years of cultivation left.
He barely lives.
My brother must hate me now
and doesn't want to see me anymore.
General Fu,
don't say that.
His Majesty
didn't blame you.
He just hopes that
one day,
you can become a good Demon King
and lead Melody Race well.
Then His Majesty
will be relieved.
Become a good Demon King
while stepping on my brother's body.
General Fu,
I know it's difficult.
But
there is no other way.
Why don't you just follow His Majesty's wish,
OK?
I will fulfill his and Luo Ning's wishes.
But in my heart,
only my brother is the Demon King,
the only one in the world.
No matter what it takes,
I will protect him.
Even if I have to use my blood and primordial spirit to pave the way for him,
I will
protect him.
Immortal Master, are you looking for me?
Do you know
why I always thwart you and Ge?
You worry that
I'll affect Luo Ge's cultivation.
Wrong.
It's because you resemble her too much.
Back then,
if she hadn't shown her kindness,
the evil spirit wouldn't be eternal.
God of the Sun...
I can no longer suppress the evil spirit.
Is the tragedy from ten thousand years ago going to happen again?
I will try my best
to improve my cultivation.
and seal the evil spirit.
Before that,
I'll try to deal with the evil
to protect myself
and others.
It was wrong ten thousand years ago.
Do you want to
let Liu Shao be like God of the Sun?
After all,
in your eyes,
I'm just
a shadow of God of the Sun.
I'm just worried that you will
repeat
the same mistake as God of the Sun.
Liu Shao,
there's something you need to know.
Luo Ge,
you and I are one.
But have you forgotten
who lives with us?
Immortal Master, you mean
I will be the same as God of the Sun.
The evil spirit appears.
Three Realms will be in chaos soon.
You are the only instrument left by God of the Moonlight.
Can you give me some hints?
Actually, few people
know that part of the story.
Moon Sword,
what happened back then?
You must know it.
God of the Sun
could have killed the evil spirit with her Crown Wheel,
but she didn't.
Why not?
At that time, God of the Sun tried to
dispel the evil spirit in God of the Moonlight,
but it only made God of the Moonlight more seriously injured.
It seemed that before the evil spirit was cleared,
God of the Moonlight would die first.
What's more dangerous is that
as the spiritual power of God of the Moonlight got weak,
the evil spirit got stronger.
In desperation,
God of the Moonlight asked
God of the Sun to kill himself.
To eliminate the evil spirit,
God of the Moonlight must die.
There was no other way.
But God of the Sun doesn't want God of the Sun to disappear.
To bring peace to Three Realms,
to protect the spirit of God of the Moonlight,
she decided to
fight with her life.
Moon Sword.
Exactly.
What are you doing?
You can't kill it like this.
I can't use Crown Wheel.
Crown Wheel will turn you into ashes.
I can't let you disappear.
So,
I took your sword.
It will protect you.
Do you know what you are doing?
I know.
Put down the sword.
Even if I am devoured and killed by Moon Sword,
I will let you live.
The evil spirit was suppressed.
Moon Sword was sealed.
God of the Sun died due to the devouring.
The strike
with all her strength
broke the heart of God of the Moonlight into two.
One half with the evil spirit was sealed under Four Seasons Monument.
The other half
which keeps God of the Moonlight's consciousness
turned into Ge.
Then God of the Moonlight remains.
But in the end, she couldn't wait for Ge to transform.
Then, there was no God of the Sun in Three Realms.
Because of her love,
the evil spirit remains for ten thousand years.
And Ge
was born because of love.
That is the truth.
So God of the Sun didn't choose to kill God of the Moonlight.
And I met Luo Ge
because of her love.
Liu Shao,
only you can save Three Realms now.
But I can't even break the seal of Sun Spirit.
What else should I do?
Liu Shao,
it is not an accident for you
to be in Immortal Palace.
Since you stepped into Immortal Palace,
I felt that she was back.
♫The wind is getting slower, while the pear flowers are dropping♫
Ten thousand years have passed.
She seemed to have left for just a moment.
♫The silver color is cold and sharp♫
♫On the top of Heaven and between reincarnation♫
Immortal Master.
♫The moon is like snow♫
Liu Shao,
you are the only one who can end this
♫I carve our appointment in three days between my eyebrows♫
It seems that the end of this catastrophe
♫I walk through time with you♫
is to let Liu Shao finish what God of the Sun didn't finish.
♫On the day when seas sink♫
Luo Ge.
♫When the moon never rests, the mortal world♫
I will soon lose my mind completely.
God of the Moonlight.
God of the Sun and I agreed that
♫I look back to realize the dream of my next life♫
three days later,
if the evil spirit is not eliminated,
she will kill me.
♫Half of my heart is yours. Half of me is missing you♫
Actually, I know that
♫I pay my life to fulfill my dream♫
♫You nag about days and nights beside my ear, but I can't hear you♫
she wants me to live,
♫The night carves the heart into poems♫
and she can't do it.
But she is wrong.
I must find a suitable person
to carry Sun Spirit
so that she can eliminate the evil spirit
in ten thousand years.
I am the one who will change your fate.
If you leave your fate to me,
♫The wind is getting slower, while the pear flowers are dropping♫
I'll give you three days of happiness.
♫The silver color is cold and sharp♫
Okay, I promise you.
So Liu Shao
is the one chosen by God of the Moonlight.
♫On the top of Heaven and between reincarnation♫
♫The moon is like snow♫
I've told you the method.
As for what to do,
you decide it yourself.
♫I carve our appointment in three days between my eyebrows♫
♫I walk through time with you♫
So
the three-day promise
shoulders all living beings.
♫On the day when seas sink♫
♫When the moon never rests, the mortal world♫
Liu Shao,
♫I look back to realize the dream of my next life♫
don't forget our promise
Remember your mission
♫Half of my heart is yours. Half of me is missing you♫
♫I pay my life to fulfill my dream♫
♫You nag about days and nights beside my ear, but I can't hear you♫
♫The night carves the heart into poems♫
♫You left my heart. You are my fate♫
♫You are like dreams as if you disappear♫
♫Two sides are round. You are like the moon at 11 pm♫
♫You are my fate♫
♫Look at the three realms. Look at the wilderness♫
In that case,
God of the Sun,
I'll do
♫Our old fate has become a cocoon♫
what you couldn't do for you.
♫The rest of life is no match  for a second♫
I'll help you solve
what you regretted.
I will protect all beings in Three Realms
♫I look back to realize the dream of my next life♫
and the heart of God of the Moonlight
for you.
♫Half of my heart is yours. Half of me is missing you♫
♫I pay my life to fulfill my dream♫
♫You nag about days and nights beside my ear, but I can't hear you♫
♫The night carves the heart into poems♫